playbb.me 2016-01-22

# Private Policy

**The Privacy of our Visitors is Important to Us**

We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should always check this page to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

**How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at [here](http://www.playbb.me/contact).

**Legal Disclaimer for Us**

No video content is held on our servers and we are in no way affiliated with the video content. The video content that is displayed originates from social video websites, such as, but not limited to Veoh, YouTube, Dailymotion and Myspace TV.

In case of copyright infringement, please directly contact the responsible parties. We operate as an index and database of anime content found publicly available on the internet, in principle conducting in the same way as yahoo. However, we strongly believes in the protection of intellectual property and would be willing to assist when possible and applicable.

Users who upload to these websites agree not to upload illegal content when creating their user accounts. We do not accept responsibility for content hosted on third party websites, nor do we upload videos ourselves or encourage others to do so. The videos are streamed directly from the third-party video sharing services mentioned above.

**Links to other Websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)
